metallica.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy | Metallica.com

###### Effective date: August 22, 2018

ANALYTICS CONSENT: Websites may ask you to accept tracking cookies to make the websites work as you expect and personalize the marketing and advertising that you see through your internet browser. Cookies alone do not personally identify you. They may gather information such as your IP address, unique cookie identifier, your location and your activities on our website.

We will only tracking cookies with your express consent. On this website, Google Tag Manager improves our ability to present users with more personalized product information. We may use other cookies in the future.

GENERAL TERMS:   
Frantic, Inc. and its affiliates (“we”) are committed to protecting and preserving your privacy. This policy, together with our Terms of Use and Conditions, and any other underlying agreements or terms, sets out the basis on which any data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. By using our website (“Site”), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also describes the manner in which we process, use and disclose information that you provide to us when you use our Site.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of information as described in this Privacy Policy. We do update this Privacy Policy from time to time so please review this Privacy Policy regularly. If we materially alter our Privacy Policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting a notice on our Site. If you do not agree with the changes, then you should stop using the Site, and you should notify us that you do not want your information used in accordance with the changes.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is a part of the Terms of Use and Conditions for this Site. To access the Terms of Use and Conditions [click here](https://www.metallica.com/terms.html).

If you would like to access, correct, amend, remove or limit the use of any of your information that has been collected and stored by us, please notify our Data Protection Officer, Vickie Strate, by emailing webmaster@metclub.com.

Information We Collect   
In operating our Site, we may collect and process the following data about you:

  1. Details of your visits to our Site and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, including your IP address, the date and time you accessed or left the Site and which pages you viewed. Some parts of our Site use cookies and other technologies to collect this information about your general internet usage. See section below ‘How We Use Cookies” to learn more.
  2. Information that you provide directly to us by filling in forms on our Site, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card billing information.
  3. Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

By submitting a telephone number to Frantic, Inc. and its affiliates you agree that a representative of Frantic, Inc. and its affiliates can contact you at the number you provide, potentially using automated technology (including texts/SMS messaging) or a pre-recorded message. Your consent is not an obligation to receive any of our products and/or services.

How We Use Cookies   
A “cookie” is a small data file that is written to your computer's hard drive by your web browser.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. If you agree, the cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer. We use this information to improve our Site and present content in the most effective manner for you and your computer. You can decline to accept cookies. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use the full functionality of your browser software or this the Site. We will use the services of outside parties to process data that we collect from cookies.

We do not track our users across time or across websites. We may use the information obtained to make decisions regarding marketing for our related businesses including (without limitation) Sweet Amber doing business as Blackened Whiskey and the charitable organization All Within My Hands brands, including.

We do not use flash cookies on our Site.

Use of Your Information   
The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our products and/or services to you in the best possible manner. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

  1. To provide you with information relating to our services and/or products and those of our related businesses including (without limitation) Sweet Amber doing business as Blackened Whiskey and the charitable organization All Within My Hands;
  2. To provide third parties with statistical information about the users of our Site;
  3. To monitor and conduct an analysis of our Site traffic and usage patterns; and
  4. To analyze trends.

Security   
To secure your information, we have put in place commercially suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on our Site.

Nonetheless, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically on our Site, and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk.

Disclosing Your Information   
Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any affiliated business entities (without limitation) Sweet Amber doing business as Blackened Whiskey and the charitable organization All Within My Hands, or third parties necessary to provide products and/or services to you, including Salesforce (our commerce and marketing platform) and Signifyd (fraudulent transaction analysis). We may also disclose your personal information to other third parties, such as:

  1. Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party, whether through bankruptcy proceedings or other sale or merger.
  2. Where we are legally required to disclose your information.
  3. When we are contractually obligated to disclose it.

Third Party Websites   
By accessing third party websites through our Site, you are consenting to the terms and privacy policies of those websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.

Users Only of Legal Age of Majority   
Our Site is designed and intended for those who have reached the age of majority (18 years of age). By using our Site, you affirm that you are at least 18 years of age or older. We are not liable for any damages that may result from a user’s misrepresentation of age.

No one under age 13 is authorized to submit or post any information, including personally identifying information, on our Site. Under no circumstances may anyone under age 13 use our Site. Parents or legal guardians of children under 13 cannot agree to these Terms on their behalf.

Contacting Us   
We welcome any queries, comments, complaints or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at:

Frantic, Inc. and its affiliates   
369-B Third Street   
PMB#194   
webmaster@metclub.com
